Sculpture Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- United States (Box 17)
  - Artists Known (Box 17)
    - Strider, Marjorie, 1934- (Box 26)
    - Stuart, Michelle, 1938- (Box 26)
    - Sugarman, George, 1912- [Slide box 154] (Box 26)
    - Sullivan, Kaylynn Twotrees, 1945- (Box 26)
    - Surls, James, 1943- (Box 26)
    - Swarz, Sahl (Box 26)
    - Tacha, Athena (Box 26)
    - Taft, Lorado, 1860-1936 (Box 26)
    - Tajiri, S. (Box 26)
    - Tasset, Tony, 1960- (Box 26)
    - Taylor, William, 1927- (Box 26)
    - Thek, Paul, 1933- (Box 26)
    - Therrien, Robert (Box 26)
    - Thiele, Robert, 1941- (Box 26)
    - Tilden, Douglas, 1860-1935 (Box 26)
    - Ti Shan Hsu (Box 26)
    - Tiravanija, Rirkrit, 1961- (Box 26)
    - Todd, Michael, 1935- (Box 26)
    - Todt Group (Box 26)
    - Tolerton, David (Box 26)
    - Tomlin, Bradley, 1899-1953 (Box 26)
    - Tong, Michael Yue, 1967- (Box 26)
    - Torres, Francesco, 1948- (Box 26)
    - Torres, Rigoberto, 1960- (Box 26)
    - Tovish, Harold, 1921- (Box 26)
    - Townley, Hugh, 1923- (Box 26)
    - Tracey, Michael, 1943- [Slide box 155] (Box 26)
    - Trova, Ernest, 1927- (Box 26)
    - Truitt, Anne, 1921- (Box 26)
    - Trumbull, John, 1756-1843 (Box 26)
    - Turrell, James (Box 26)
    - Tuttle, Richard, 1941- (Box 26)
    - Twombly, CY., 1929- (Box 26)
    - Ukeles, Mierle Laderman, 1939- (Box 26)
    - Umlauf, Charles, 1911- (Box 26)
    - Valintine, DeWain (Box 26)
    - Van Buren, Richard (Box 26)
    - Van Tongeren, Herk, 1943-1987 (Box 26)
    - Velz, Edin, 1951- (Box 26)
    - Viola, William, 1951- [Slide boxes 155-156] (Box 26)
    - Volk, Leonard, 1828-1895 [Slide box 156] (Box 26)
    - Vonnoh, Bessie P., 1872-1955 (Box 26)
    - Von Rydingsvaard, Ursula (Box 26)
    - Von Schlegell, David (Box 26)
    - Voulkos, Peter, 1924- (Box 26)
    - Walker, Kelley, act.c.1999 (Box 26)
    - Walters, Carl, 1883-1955 [Slide box 157] (Box 27)
    - Warashina, Patti, 1939- (Box 27)
    - Warburg, Eugene, 1826-1859 (Box 27)
    - Ward, John Quincy A., 1830-1910 (Box 27)
    - Waring, Pagot, 1910- (Box 27)
    - Warneke, Heinz, 1895-1983 (Box 27)
    - Warhol, Andy, 1931- (Box 27)
    - Warner, Olin Levi, 1844-1896 (Box 27)
    - Watkins, Tim (Box 27)
    - Watts, Robert, 1923-1988 (Box 27)
    - Weber, Max, 1881-1961 (Box 27)
    - Webster, Derek, 1934- (Box 27)
    - Webster, Meg (Box 27)
    - Weems, Carrie Mar, 1953- (Box 27)
    - Weinberg, Elbert, 1928- (Box 27)
    - Weinbren, Grahame & Roberta Friedman (Box 27)
    - Weiner, Lawrence Charles, 1940- (Box 27)
    - Welch, Roger (Box 27)
    - Wender, Barbara, act.c.1970 (Box 27)
    - Werner, Nat, 1907- (Box 27)
    - Westermann, H.C., 1922- [Slide box 158] (Box 27)
    - Wharton, Margaret Agnes, 1943- (Box 27)
    - Whirehurst, Byron Lee (Box 27)
    - Whitman, Robert, 1925- (Box 27)
    - Whitney, Gertrude Vanderbilt, 1876-1942 (Box 27)
    - Wholley, Jay N. (Box 27)
    - Wiley, William T., 1937- (Box 27)
    - Wilke, Hannah, 1940- (Box 27)
      Xx Photography
    - Williams, Sue, 1954- [Slide box 159] (Box 27)
    - Wilmarth, Christopher, 1943- (Box 27)
    - Wilson, Ed, 1925- (Box 27)
    - Wilson, Fred, 1954- (Box 27)
    - Wilson, John, 1922- (Box 27)
    - Wilson, Millie, 1948- (Box 27)
    - Wines, James (Box 27)
    - Winsor, Jacqueline, 1941- (Box 27)
    - Wirsum, Karl, 1939- (Box 27)
    - Wodiczko, Krzysztof, 1943- (Box 27)
    - Wolff, Kevin, 1955- (Box 27)
    - Womanhouse Installation (Box 27)
      Xx Chicago, J.
      Xx Schapiro, M.
    - Wood, Steve (Box 27)
    - Woodman, Betty (Box 27)
    - Wye, Joan, act.c.1970 (Box 27)
    - Yonemoto, Bruce, 1949- (Box 27)
    - Yoshimura, Fumio (Box 27)
    - Young, Mahonri, 1877- (Box 27)
    - Yuskavage, Lisa, 1962- (Box 27)
    - Zittel, Andrea, 1965- (Box 27)
    - Zogbaum, Wilfrid, 1915- [Slide box 160] (Box 27)
    - Zorach, William, 1887-1966 (Box 27)
    - Zwillinger, Rhonda (Box 27)